I can't see anybody now though. Can you see everyone? Okay, never mind. Can
everyone see that? Okay, my screen. Yes. Okay, so we thought we'd do a little
Zoom today on credits and the credit system.
Because I think this has been requested, hasn't it, by a few people? And there
's a lot of confusion and it's just good to just have a recap and go over
everything to do with credits.
So we're going to talk through a couple of different ways that you can work out
your credit, load of information about the payroll and the credit system, and
you can ask any questions.
Yeah, maybe if anyone wants to come in at the end, the mentors or anyone else
and just give any tips or anything we've missed to do with their payroll and
you know, you know, any tips for anybody else.
That sound okay with everyone. Okay.
So, this is the basic credit breakdown. So, one credit equals 56.5 p.
So, for us to be completely transparent, which we always like to be and this
recording will be available on the website soon so you'll be able to watch it
back if you ever want to recap as well.
So, the ethical community takes 10% of the money that you make, payroll takes 3
.5% and AdultWork takes 30%. If you weren't in a group, AdultWork takes a
larger percentage so all in, you're only paying 7.5% overall to be with the
ethical community.
I hope that makes sense everyone.
Do you want to do this bit Georgia.
Yeah sure.
So payroll removes your credits and pays you so you don't have to do anything.
This is like a question that we do get a lot. And so yeah, once you're set up
with payroll, that's that you don't ever have to worry about transferring the
credits.
They may remove the credits from your AdultWork account weekly or less often,
but you are paid daily. So sometimes your credit statement will show the
credits you've already been paid for.
So yeah, basically this one, you know, might say you've got 400 credits in your
account and then the next day you get paid on those credits, yet the balance
still says 400 and that's just because they're just sitting in there for a
while until the payroll company take them all out.
And so yeah, try not to get confused with that.
And you can be paid up to any time up to 9pm on any day you're due a payment.
So yeah, that's another one sometimes it gets about midday and some of the
girls worry that the payments haven't went in yet.
That's totally fine. As it can go in anytime. It does usually go in quite handy
as you know.
But yeah, don't worry if it's a little bit later than usual.
Okay.
So, here is the video where Georgia is going to describe how to calculate your
credits.
So, I thought I could play the video and then maybe we can have a little chat
about it after or if there's any questions or anything because I know that it's
not.
Well, if you're anything like me it's not the most straightforward thing.
So, let's play the video and then we'll have a little chat maybe afterwards.
Hi everyone. In today's video I'm going to explain how the credits work and how
to work out what you've made on any given day. So first of all, I've logged
into my profile.
And now I'm going to go to my details credits and click here on credit
statement.
This shows all of the transactions and all of the credits that you've made
since the very start of your webcam journey.
So, here, this last page is the most recent in transactions and most recent
credits that you've made.
So, what we're going to do today, I'm going to show you exactly how to work out
what you've made on any given day. I'm going to choose the 5th of August.
So, to work out what you've made on any given day, you need to subtract what
you started on that day from what you ended on.
So, let's start on what we ended on. So, if we want to work out what we made on
the 5th of August, we will go to the very last transaction on the 5th which is
here.
And we're going to go along and see what it was, what we ended on. Okay, so as
you can see here, we ended the 5th on 228.24 credits.
So, we're going to put that into our calculator. Okay, I've now put that into
my calculator.
Now, I'm going to see what I started that day on.
So, as you can still see here, there's still transactions on the 5th here. So,
we need to go back at page to see if there are any more. So, we just click the
shadow to go back one page.
So, we need to find the 5th of the 8th here. So, we go down, we should be able
to find it. Okay, there we go.
There are a couple of transactions here on the 5th of the 8th. So, we just need
the very first transaction that's all we need to worry about.
And we just need to see what the balance was at the very start of the day.
So, as we can see, the balance is 8.55 credits. So, now we need to subtract
that from that final balance.
So, at the mark, I have in my calculator what we ended that day on. And now, I
'm going to subtract 8.55 from that.
So, I have 228.24 take away 8.55. And that equals 219.69 credits. So, that's
how many credits we made on the 5th.
And we're not finished yet because it's how many credits you made.
So, now we have how much that is in pounds, how much money you should expect in
your bank the next day.
We now need to take away 43.5%. So, I'm going to do that on my calculator now.
So, that leaves us with 124.12 pounds. So, that's how much you should have in
your bank the next day.
So, yes, it's very simple to work out. You just work out what you ended the day
on, subtract what you started the day on.
And then, whatever that remaining balance is, take away 43.5%. And that's how
much pounds you've made that day.
I'm now going to explain a couple more things on the credit statement.
So, as you can see here, balance goes down to zero. And again, here. And it
says it's a group transfer.
This basically is our payroll company transferring all of the credits out of
your account.
This happens every week or so. So, don't worry about it. It may happen when you
're online. It may happen halfway through the week.
It really doesn't matter. And it's not something that you need to worry about.
The payroll company just have to transfer your credit cell as obviously they
need to take the money out of the profile to then pay you.
Here as well, it says available for transfer now. You don't need to worry about
this either. You do not need to transfer your credits.
Our payroll company do everything for you. They work out how much you've made,
where to pay you, how to pay you, and everything that comes in between you.
But you don't need to worry about your credits at all because our payroll
company, like I said, do everything for you and pay you daily.
But if you do want to check one final thing to remember with your credits, we
pay you daily, like I said, but if you don't hit 65 credits, you won't get paid
the next day.
They will just sit in your volunteer until you push over 65 and then you'll
then get paid the next day.
And the day ends at 12 o'clock midnight. So bear that in mind, we're going to
wait and go to how much you've made.
I hope all that makes sense. And if you've had any more questions, please ask
your mentor.
Okay.
Ladies, do we have any questions? Does anybody want to ask anything about that?
Is anybody unsure? I can't see anyone right now. So if you can just put your
hand up or, or just speak.
Anybody has any questions about it?
I can see everyone and everyone's just shaking their head to say we don't have
any questions.
But yeah, I just wanted to say, I don't know how it played for you.
You, you, you, you guys, but on my end, it was a little bit blurry, the video.
But it is on the welcome course as well. It's on week one of the welcome course
.
I've just re uploaded it now because I just know the videos have had a bit of
trouble, but that one's back on there and the rest will be soon.
And so yeah, it's on week one of the welcome course, if you need to watch it
and see, see it, but I think just the voice explaining it's probably enough
anyway.
But yeah, just what I like is know that.
Yeah, and I think the mentors have it anyway to send to you.
But yeah, so you can watch that elsewhere. Sorry if it wasn't very good quality
.
Okay, everyone.
Okay.
So we're not going for that again.
Just show you a different way to do it. So this is the way that I've always
kept a track on my credits.
And the reason that we've not shown you this way before is because it's not 100
% accurate.
So if you are ever thinking that your credits might be wrong or you really not
sure and you want to get an accurate, you know, really accurate region of
exactly how many credits you've made, then always do it the way that George is
just shown in that video.
But if you want to just go on and literally take two seconds to see what you've
made that day, you know, and the next estimate of what you've made.
And then this is another way to do it that I've always used because I've just
found it really easy and simple and quick.
So on the next screen, I'll show you the credit activity page so you can see it
.
But basically, you log in to add a work, you click on my details tab at the top
, click on credits, and then click on credit activity. So that'll take you to
the credit activity page.
So from that page, rather than seeing every single transaction like you do on
the, the other page, you'll just see what you've made each day.
So you can put in any date range, whether it's this week, a year, whatever, and
see how many credits you made each day and a total over that date range.
When it shows you the total, you just take off 5% and that's how many credits
that you've made during that time scale, whatever time scale you put in.
So this is a quick and easy way to get an estimate of your credits over any
length of time. The reason it's just an estimate is because it doesn't account
for the 5% out of work faculty fee that I mentioned above that's why you take
off 5%.
Any items that you've sold or any tips that you've got, and any positioning
fees that you've spent. So if you've spent money to be on the front page, then
that won't have come off that balance.
So this is just what you made on CAM.
It does break things down a little so you can see what you made on CAM, what
you made on the phone, and what you made on IM. So it does, it does tell you
those things.
But yeah, just to be aware that you take 5% off it, and it doesn't account for
all the little things like positioning and tips and stuff like that.
But I think it's just a really quick way to, you know, taking off 5% is
basically half, it's just a bit more than half, isn't it? So I've always just
like halved it and that's pretty much what I've always got.
So it's just an extra way, if you've just got a couple of seconds, just to look
at roughly what you made.
Did you want to add anything to that, Georgia or?
No, I didn't want to add anything to that bit to be honest, this bit I've never
actually done it this way so I won't add anything, whatever I say we'll
probably be right.
So yeah, I'll let you take this bit.
Yeah, well I thought I'd just put, so this is my full transparency, this is my
credit activity that I just bought on here yesterday.
So you can see from September, you can see the breakdown of what I've made, so
it tells you private gallery, movies, webcam, direct ham and all that.
At the end of the totals, and then at the bottom you can see the final total.
I like this page because I know you have to take off the 5% but it's a really
good way to like motivate yourself as well because sometimes you can see there
on mine.
Sometimes I've been online and made 20 credits or 8 credits on one day and like
you might end up feeling a bit crappy, you know, we all have quiet days but
then other days have made like 200 credits or whatever and I can see how much
it adds up to over whatever length of time I put in.
So, I find it quite nice to look back, you know, over a month and see how much
I've actually made that month because it's normally more than I realised.
Why it doesn't work sometimes?
What do you say?
Why it doesn't work sometimes, why it's not accurate?
I think Kirsty showed me that one the same, isn't it Kirsty? Did you show me
this date? That's how is it, isn't it?
Yeah, it is accurate, it's just we need to take off the 5% and there's no tips,
it doesn't account for tips and it doesn't account for bidding so if you spent
money on bidding that won't have come off this balance so that needs to come
off it as well.
Right, okay. So, it's not 100% accurate but it's pretty close. Yeah, okay.
So, is it the same ratio? I mean, I haven't sold anything yet or set up a pay
gallery or anything like that.
Is it the same ratio across the board, is it, for everything? Right, okay.
Yeah, so one credit is always worth the same amount.
0.56, yeah, okay. Yeah, yeah, and there's another, it's probably worth
mentioning as well because on the video, Georgia explains it that you work out
your credits by taking away however many percent it is, isn't it?
Taking away 47% real, all I do is when the credits, it's like, I don't know, 65
credits. I just, I've just times it by 0.56, and it goes you're like 85 pound
40 or something like that. So, that's just the way I do it.
I don't know, I think it's right.
Yeah, I just have always done, you know, whatever my credit is times 0.565.
Yeah, yeah.
And I do it minus 43.5% on my calculator. So, but it works out the same, it's
just these two days, two ways of doing it.
Yeah, yeah. Sorry, can you just go back to that previous page and can I, I'd
like to ask a question if that's okay.
And you know you said, you just take a look at the total and then take off 5%.
So, so let's say you want to want to see what you made on the second of the
nine for the very first transaction and it says 1 5 1.11.
So then you just take away 5% from that and that gives you it in pounds.
Really? So it's, that's not showing us credits then that's just showing like
the pounds without the faculty fee off it kinds of thing.
No, no, it is, it is credit. It is credit. So you still need to work out how
much your credits are in pound.
But you take away 43.5% adds 5% and then another 5% on top with us you take
away so 48.5% instead.
Yeah, which is very close to half. So pretty much I just look at it.
Yeah, so you just you just have it down here. Yeah, I usually do because I've
usually spent a couple of credits on position in as well, which usually makes
it pretty much percent.
Yeah, but that's just an estimate. You know, it's not like if you ever query a
new credits or if you're not sure then it's always best to do it the full way,
but it's just a really quick way to think, oh, half of that is credit.
So, and then I roughly know how much that is.
Yeah. Okay, cool. Yeah, I wasn't sure but could you said about the 5% I just
thought to myself was our 5% on top of the 43.5. So yeah, it is okay cool. So
basically half.
So you're just far but you're on the wind inside, aren't you, because you're
going to get five, you know, six or seven more on your.
Yeah, and sometimes, you know, I spend that much on on positioning over the
course of a day.
Yeah, I'm with you. Yeah. Yeah.
So if you sold some, I don't know, photos and stuff and you have like 20
credits in there. It just shows up as I prefer the sale of 20 credits does it.
Yeah.
So anything on there will just add up and then on the totals on the right hand
side, it'll tell you the total what you've made up of everything.
Yeah, just the tips aren't added, which I didn't realise because I, because I
went to payroll to ask them if this nation is definitely right before I did
this.
It's not added on there, which I was surprised about, but.
So what happens is the tips, son, if you get the tips?
Well, you still get paid for them, but they just don't show on this screen some
reason, it's just not a thing to show you.
Yeah. Yeah.
So yeah, so that's that.
And then just a few things to remember, I think we said most of these anyway,
but so to use the credit activity only for a quick estimate.
So the one that I've just shown you, if you want to work out exactly, you know,
to the hence how much you've made, then do it the proper way.
Pay can go in any time up to nine, but we do say that if, you know, if it
normally comes in early and if by like four o'clock it's not coming in, then
feel free to message a mentor and we, when we can message payroll for you and
just give them an urgency.
Okay.
A cut off the next day pay is 35 pounds or it rolls over, like George said, you
can request weekly or monthly pay if you prefer, so it's daily pay, but you
have an option to change it if you'd rather have it any other way.
Let your mentor know any change of username or bank details, because payroll
won't won't know to pay you if you change you use name on other work.
And obviously if you change a bank details with those as well.
And yeah, if there's an issue, just contact your mentor.
And so that's it from the PowerPoint.
Take this off so I can see everyone again.
Does anyone have anything that they'd like to ask or add.
About credits about with another credits or payroll.
Can I add something quick.
Yeah.
And what I do, we're always check my bank first.
Sometimes if you get in daily pay and that confusing sometimes I'll be paid
five times a week in terms of a week.
So if I've not been, or I think I haven't been paying in a couple of days or
whatever, I'll go on to my bank.
And then if I've been paid 29 September, for example, I then go on to my credit
statement and count everything from 29 September onwards.
Because if you, you know, if you just start counting randomly, you might get
the amounts wrong.
And if you've been paid on the 29th, it doesn't include what you've earned on
the 29th.
So I will go on the 29th and just start counting like last year yesterday I was
on.
We've got paid today, but then when I've been on today.
I've got a last night started before midnight ended after midnight.
So I've got, I started today with 35 credit without even realising and they,
you know, could have got lost in my mind somewhere.
So just another little tear.
Maybe check the bank first.
Yeah.
Thank you, Sophie.
That's a really good point.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
But when if I'm using that credit activity, I'll always call on when I last got
paid.
Like Sophie says, the thing about what that says.
I do the same when I'm checking the credit activity.
I always go check when I was last paid and I always go from the day I was paid.
Yeah.
Just see how many credits I'm owing.
Like if I'm doing over three days and I've gone, I've had a slow day.
I always check from the day I got paid last, not the week before, once before.
Yeah.
I'm probably sorry.
I've got really bad code and you don't want to see my face.
Trust me.
And I was just going to say exactly the same as not safe and cursive.
Just said, I think a few girls are getting a bit confused where they're just
seeing like the at the end of their statement.
It says, I don't know, like 450 credits and they're not sort of working out
that they've already made them paid like almost half or three quarters of that.
You've got to look back to when you was last paid and then go from that date.
So I think that's a little bit confusing for a few people that and then when
the credits get taken out, they're like, Oh, I had 400.
It's gone.
Where has it gone?
And just try not to worry that like it's disappeared.
It will never disappear.
You'll always be paid for like what you've earned 100%.
You know, like that's never going to happen.
We're not going to just suddenly lose 400 credits or anything like that.
Yeah.
So just bear that in mind.
It will empty out of your account.
I think they do it on a Tuesday, don't they?
Sometimes they change it.
I'm not sure every week or two weeks.
But yeah, try not to worry about that and just work out.
So from one date to the next of what you've earned.
Yeah.
I hope that makes sense.
Thank you, Sammy.
And I was just thinking as well, probably worth mentioning, if you haven't been
on for months, like if you haven't been on for ages, like, obviously life just
gets in the way sometimes.
And you go on and then you're not paid the next day when you think you should
have just message your mentor or me and or don't meet and help payroll because
sometimes if someone's not been on for a really long time, then they do need a
nudge to like check that account.
That does happen sometimes, isn't it?
Yeah.
I think that's all from.
Anybody else?
I don't know.
No, we're all good.
Okay, ladies.
Well, that was short and easy, wasn't it?
Um, like she says, we'll have the website soon, along with all the other videos
we've been working on that this week.
And then our next call is going to be the.
Can master class, I think, isn't it?
Yeah.
So that's Wednesday, the 90 for October at nine p.m.
Yeah, that'd be a good one.
Yeah.
Oh, my sofa comes that day.
I'm so excited.
I hope you guys can see it.
I'm sorry.
Okay, ladies.
Have a fabulous day.
And you.